Guide to the Peter Palmquist Collection of Women in Photography
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Biographical Materials, 1971-2003; Series I; (219 boxes)
  - Volumes About Women Photographers in General, (75 volumes)
    - Volumes compiled by Palmquist
      - Women in California Photography 1900-1920, undated; 10 volumes (Box 183-192)
      - Photo-Fighters: Women Photographers in World War II, 1993 (Box 193)
      - Women Photographers: Miscellaneous Listings and Accounts Arranged by State and County, circa 1992 (Box 194)
      - Biographical and Resource Index, Volume A (December 1996), 1996 Dec (Box 195)
      - Biography and Resource Index A-Z as of January 1, 2000, 2000 Jan 1 (Box 196)
    - General Works about Women Photographers by Other Authors
      - Janis, Eugenia Parry, "To Collect the Art of Women: The Jane Reese Williams Photography Collection," Museum of Fine Arts, Museum of New Mexico, Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1991 (Box 197)
      - Meister, Laura Ilise, "Missing from the Picture: Boston Women Photographers, 1880-1920", 1998 (Box 198)
        Master of Arts Thesis, Tufts University
      - Rosenblum, Naomi, "World History of Women in Photography," manuscript, 1993 (Box 199)
        Published as A History of Women Photographers (1994)
      - Skidmore, Colleen Marie, "Women in Photography at the Notman Studio, Montreal (Canada), 1856-1881", 1999 (Box 200)
        Doctoral dissertation, University of Alberta
      - Till, Jennifer E., "Seven Female Photographers of the Oklahoma and Indian Territories, 1889 to 1907", 1999 (Box 201)
        Master of Arts Thesis, Oklahoma State University
    - Bibliographies of Works About Women Photographers
      - Bibliography of Articles By and About Women in Photography 1840-1990, Third Edition, 1999 Feb (Box 202)
      - Bibliography of Articles By and About Women in Photography 1840-1990, Fourth Edition, 2000 Jul (Box 203)
      - Books By or About Women Photographers, 1992 Dec; unbound volume (Box 204)
      - Inventories and Bibliographes of Books By or About Women Photographers in the Women in Photography International Archive, 1996 Jan 1-2002 Nov 1; 9 volumes (Box 205-213)
        Consists of 8 volumes and 1 variant edition of the December 1997 volume
  - Publicity about Exhibitions and Lectures, 1978-2001; (1 box)
    The subseries is arranged by the institution sponsoring the exhibition or lecture.
    This subseries primarily consists of individual postcards or catalogs, sent to Palmquist that document exhibitions and lectures about women photographers in general at various museums and art galleries, as well as sale catalogs from booksellers and moving film distributors.
    Publicity about individual photographers is primarily located in the biographical files subseries.
    - Albin O. Kuhn Library, 1995-1996 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Bryn Mawr College, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Film Fund, 1978-1980 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Houston Center for Photography, 1994-1997 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - International Center of Photography, 1997 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - L. Clarice Davis, 1995 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Library of Congress, 1995 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Museum of New Mexico, 1998 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Musée de Art Américain Giverny, 2001 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - New Day Films, circa 1979 (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - New York Public Library, 1996-1997 (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Professional Women Photographers, 1996 (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - Royal Photographic Society, 1991 (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco Camerawork, 1998 (Box 214, Folder 14)
    - Signals Interchange Studios, 1994 (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - Simmons College, 1997-2001 (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - Southern Arts Federation, 1995 (Box 214, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, (1 box)
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by the surname of the correspondent.
    This subseries consists of correspondence between Palmquist and his assistants with historians, museum personnel, and other researchers. A significant portion of the correspondence concerns his interest in pioneer women photographers and may relate to a planned project documenting women photographers active before 1866.
    Several folders solely document the contact information for the individual
    - Araújo, Nuno Borges de (Box 215, Folder 18)
    - Auer, Michael (Box 215, Folder 19)
    - Bailey, Linda (Box 215, Folder 20)
    - Bladvinsdóttir, Lára (Box 215, Folder 21)
    - Brown, Rebecca (Box 215, Folder 22)
    - Boom, Mattie (Box 215, Folder 23)
    - Boyd, Torin (Box 215, Folder 24)
    - Busch, Katia (Box 215, Folder 25)
    - Chiesa, Gabriele (Box 215, Folder 26)
    - Cowen, Chester R. (Box 215, Folder 27)
    - Cox, Julian (Box 215, Folder 28)
    - Dahlman, Eva (Box 215, Folder 29)
    - Daneman, Andrew (Box 215, Folder 30)
    - Denny, Margaret (Box 215, Folder 31)
    - Driver, Julia L. (Box 215, Folder 32)
    - Eltzroth, E. Lee (Box 215, Folder 33)
    - Fayles, Robert (Box 215, Folder 34)
    - Fontanella, Lee (Box 215, Folder 35)
    - Fredgant, Don (Box 215, Folder 36)
    - Gersamia, Giorgi (Box 215, Folder 37)
    - Hammar, Stefan (Box 215, Folder 38)
    - Hearnshaw, John (Box 215, Folder 39)
    - Herder, Hans de (Box 215, Folder 40)
    - Holm-Johnsen, Hanne (Box 215, Folder 41)
    - Hostetler, Joan E. (Box 215, Folder 42)
    - Huijsmans, Dionysius P. (Box 215, Folder 43)
    - Jiabao, Wu (Box 215, Folder 44)
    - Jonge, Ingrid Fischer (Box 215, Folder 45)
    - Joseph, Steven (Box 215, Folder 46)
    - Kailbourn, Thomas (Box 215, Folder 47)
    - Knape, Gunilla (Box 215, Folder 48)
    - Kolta, Magda (Box 215, Folder 49)
    - Krabbe Meyer, Mette Kia (Box 215, Folder 50)
    - Krempp, Cendrine (Box 215, Folder 51)
    - Lebrec, Yves (Box 215, Folder 52)
    - Lööf, Lars Olof (Box 215, Folder 53)
    - Lowe, Stephen C. (Box 215, Folder 54)
    - Matovcik, A. (Box 215, Folder 55)
    - Meller, Taina (Box 215, Folder 56)
    - Mesquit, Teresa (Box 215, Folder 57)
    - Mgquba, Sibusisiwe (Box 215, Folder 58)
    - Monsanto, Christel (Box 215, Folder 59)
    - Morris, Richard (Box 215, Folder 60)
    - Nordström, Alison (Box 215, Folder 61)
    - Okatsuka, Akiko (Box 215, Folder 62)
    - Pelizzari, Maria Antonella (Box 215, Folder 63)
    - Peterson, Carl (Box 215, Folder 64)
    - Pinet, Hélène (Box 215, Folder 65)
    - Retter Vargas, Yolanda (Box 215, Folder 66)
    - Reynaud, Françoise (Box 215, Folder 67)
    - Roberts, Pam (Box 215, Folder 68)
    - Robb, Frances Osborn (Box 215, Folder 69)
    - Sandbye, Mette (Box 215, Folder 70)
    - Saretzky, Gary (Box 215, Folder 71)
    - Schaaf, Larry J. (Box 215, Folder 72)
    - Shaozhong, Lin (Box 215, Folder 73)
    - Simpson, Roddy (Box 215, Folder 74)
    - Sismis, Milan (Box 215, Folder 75)
    - Stevenson, Sara (Box 215, Folder 76)
    - Thage, Tove (Box 215, Folder 77)
    - Timby, Kim (Box 215, Folder 78)
    - Tinder, David V. (Box 215, Folder 79)
    - Turazzi, Maria Inez (Box 215, Folder 80)
    - Turley, Raymond V. (Box 215, Folder 81)
    - Webb, David (Box 215, Folder 82)
    - Webb, Virginia-Lee (Box 215, Folder 83)
    - Wright, Peggy G. (Box 215, Folder 84)
    - Wyller, Elin Harriet (Box 215, Folder 85)
    - Xanthakis, Alkis X. (Box 215, Folder 86)
- Photographic Materials, 1971-2003; Series II; (222 boxes)
  Series II is organized into five subseries: Photographic Materials; Photograph Albums; Cased Photographs and Fragile Photographic Materials; Audiovisual Materials; and Oversize Photographic and Biographical Materials.
  This series consists of photographic materials collected by Palmquist that were created by or document individual women photographers. It consists of vintage photographic prints created by photographers, as well as a significant quantity of copy photographs created by Palmquist of vintage photographic prints. The series documents the breadth of work by women photographers from the middle of the nineteenth century to the late twentieth century. Works by a photographer may appear in multiple subseries.
  For most of the listed photographers, the collection has only a few photographs. However, there are significant quantities of photographs by Laura Adams Armer, Betty Nettis Bennett, Penny Brogden, Juliette C. Cropley, Emma B. Freeman, Grace Chandler Horn, Charlotte D. Mansfield, Mary Stella Mowbray, Eugenia Henrietta Polos, and Marion Van Ronk.
  The subseries, Photographs of Women, in Series III, also contains photographic materials, although mostly by male photographers depicting women. Original photographs by women photographers also appear in Series IV, Women in Photography International Records.
  Specific dates of materials or image creation dates were not captured during processing.
  Each individual with photographic materials in this series has a a biographical file in Series I.
  - Photographic Materials, (117 boxes)
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by the surname of the photographer or the corporate name of the studio.
    This subseries consists of vintage photographic prints, copy photographs, 35mm color slides, photographic negatives, associated publications, and ephemera. Photographic materials with dimensions larger than 22 x 29 cm (8.7 x 11.4 in.) are located in the Oversize Photographic and Biographical Materials subseries.
    - Abraham, Ruth, 1 photographic print (Box 216, Folder 87)
    - Abrams, Roxanne, 2 color slides (Box 216, Folder 88)
    - Adam, Alice, 1 serial (Box 216, Folder 89)
    - Adams, Kelly Serat (born 1977), 1 inkjet print (Box 216, Folder 90)
    - Adams, Virginia, 1 serial (Box 216, Folder 91)
      Biographical/Historical note
      Also known as Virginia Rose Best Adams or Mrs. Ansel Adams
    - Addis, A. S., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 216, Folder 92)
    - Advocat, Keri (1974-1997), 3 color photographic prints (Box 216, Folder 93)
    - Aguilar, Laura (born 1959), 5 color 35mm slides and 1 serial (Box 216, Folder 94)
    - Ahlgren, Elise, 14 photographic prints (Box 216, Folder 95)
    - Aiken, Mary A. (1917-2005), 52 photographic prints and 0.1 linear feet of papers (Box 217, Folder 96-106)
      Also known as Mary Aiken Barbour or Mrs. Carl P. Barbour
    - Akimoto, Misako (born 1939), 8 photographic prints (Box 216, Folder 107)
    - Albertini, Margery, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 216, Folder 108)
    - Albery, Reba J., 1 photographic print (Box 216, Folder 109)
    - Albright, Emma L., Mrs. (circa 1850-1912), 4 photographic prints (Box 216, Folder 110)
      Also known as Mrs. John G. Albright, Emma L. Luse, or Mrs. Franc Luse Albright
    - Aldrich, Alma Lee, 1 photographic print (Box 216, Folder 111)
    - Alexander, Vikky (born 1959), 1 serial (Box 216, Folder 112)
    - Alfred, Harriet N., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 216, Folder 113)
      Also known as H. N. Alfred or H. N. Alford
    - Allard, Georgia A., Mrs., 3 photographic prints and 1 color photographic print (Box 216, Folder 114)
      Also known as Mrs. G. A. Allard or Mrs. G. S. Allard
    - Allen, Hildur Peterson (1888-1927), 2 photographic prints (Box 216, Folder 115)
      Also known as Hildur E. A. Peterson Frey Allen
    - Allen, Laura T., Mrs., 15 tintypes and 5 photographic prints (Box 216, Folder 116)
      Also known as Mrs. B. G. Allen, Mrs. Bennett Graham Allen, Mrs. L. T. Allen, Wing & Allen, Allen & Hay, or the Allen & Company
    - Allen, M. H., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 218, Folder 117)
      Also known as M. H. Allen & Lady
    - Allen, Mariette Pathy (born 1940), 1 color 35mm slide (Box 218, Folder 118)
    - Allen, Mary, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 218, Folder 119)
      Also known as Mrs. George D. Allen or Mrs. M. Allen
    - Allen, Palma, 10 color photographic prints and 10 color inkjet prints (Box 218, Folder 120)
    - Allen, Pamela, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 218, Folder 121)
    - Allen, Sisters, 8 color photographic prints (Box 218, Folder 122)
      Also known as Frances S. Allen or Mary E. Allen
    - Allert, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 218, Folder 123)
    - Alzner, Ella, 1 photographic print (Box 218, Folder 124)
    - Ambrogi, Patricia (born 1950), 1 catalog and 1 serial (Box 218, Folder 125)
      Also known as Patti Ambrogi
    - Amedé, Hildur, 1 photographic print (Box 218, Folder 126)
    - Amir, Lee, 2 photographic prints (Box 218, Folder 127)
    - Andersen, Eline, 3 photographic prints (Box 218, Folder 128)
    - Andersen, Hanna, Miss, 2 photographic prints (Box 218, Folder 129)
      Also known as Hannah Andersen, Miss Andersen's Photographic Studio, or The Misses Andersen
    - Anderson, Amanda, 1 photographic print (Box 218, Folder 130)
      Also known as Mrs. Hugh Anderson
    - Anderson, Bröderna, 1 photographic print (Box 218, Folder 131)
    - Anderson, Frances E., Mrs. (1916-2005), 1 color photographic print, 1 color inkjet print, and 2 serials (Box 218, Folder 132)
      Also known as Frances E. Peterson Anderson or Mrs. Charles Anderson
    - Anderson, Hilda, 5 photographic prints (Box 218, Folder 133)
    - Anderson, L. S., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 218, Folder 134)
    - Anderson, Louise, 1 photographic print (Box 218, Folder 135)
    - Andersson, Agnes, 1 photographic print (Box 218, Folder 136)
    - Andrén, Edith, 1 photographic print (Box 218, Folder 137)
    - Andrews, Sasha, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 218, Folder 138)
    - Andruss, Dolly B., Mrs., 25 photographic prints (Box 218, Folder 139)
      Also known as Mrs. William B. Andruss or Mrs. William B. Andrews
    - Angel, Selma, 3 photographic prints (Box 218, Folder 140)
    - Ankarcrona, Anna, 1 photographic print (Box 218, Folder 141)
    - Apple, Jacki, 3 color inkjet prints and 14 color 35mm slides (Box 219, Folder 142)
    - Archer, D. J., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 219, Folder 143)
      Also known as D. M. Archer
    - Arfvidson, Signe, 2 photographic prints (Box 219, Folder 144)
    - Armer, Laura Adams, Mrs. (1874-1963), 440 photographic prints, 2 color photographic prints, and 2 dismantled books (Box 220-221, Folder 145-162)
      Also known as Laura May Armer, Laura May Adams Armer, or Mrs. Sidney Armer
    - Arnesen, Jenny, 2 photographic prints (Box 219, Folder 163)
      Also known as Jenny Arnesen & Co. or Frøknene Arnesen & Young
    - Arnesen, Petrine, 2 photographic prints (Box 219, Folder 164)
    - Arnold, Eve (born 1913), 1 photographic print (Box 219, Folder 165)
      Also known as Eve Cohen Arnold
    - Ashworth, E. M., Miss, 1 serial (Box 219, Folder 166)
    - Asker, Julie, 4 photographic prints (Box 219, Folder 167)
    - Atwood, H. A., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 219, Folder 168)
    - Auger, Lina, Miss (1865-1954), 62 stereographs (Box 222, Folder 168)
      Also known as Lena Auger
    - Augspurg, Anita (1857-1943), 2 photographic prints (Box 219, Folder 169)
      Also known as Atelier Elvira
    - Austin, Alice, 3 photographic prints and 1 color photographic print (Box 219, Folder 170)
    - Averill, Ellen, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 219, Folder 171)
    - Avery, Abbie, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 219, Folder 172)
    - Axling, Agnes, 1 photographic print (Box 219, Folder 173)
    - Ayers, Elizabeth M., Miss (born 1861), 45 photographic prints (Box 223, Folder 174-177)
      Also known as Lizzie Ayers
    - Ayers, W. C., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 219, Folder 178)
    - Ayres, Katharine Scott Graves (born 1876), 1 book (Box 219, Folder 179)
      General note
      NOS, 20090623
      Also known as Katharine S. Ayres
    - B., R. W., 1 photographic print (Box 219, Folder 180)
    - Baadsgaard, Jennie, Mrs. (1893-1978), 34 photographic prints and 2 film negatives (Box 219, Folder 181)
    - Backgren, Karin, 1 photographic print (Box 219, Folder 182)
    - Bacon, Pat, 1 serial (Box 219, Folder 183)
    - Bailey, Ethel Phoebe, Miss (born 1867), 2 photographic prints (Box 219, Folder 184)
    - Baird, Melinda K., 1 photographic print (Box 219, Folder 185)
      Also known as Malinda C. Baird
    - Baker, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 224, Folder 186)
    - Baker, Edith M., Mrs. (1872-1952), 12 photographic prints (Box 224, Folder 187)
      Also known as Mrs. Ray Jerome Baker
    - Baker, Lenora, Mrs. (1915-1998), 2 color photographic prints (Box 224, Folder 188)
    - Baker, Maud Davis, Mrs. (1863-1930), 2 photographic prints (Box 224, Folder 189)
    - Baker, Viroque Davis, Miss (1889-1980), 1 photographic print (Box 224, Folder 190)
    - Balch, Eliza, 2 photographic prints (Box 224, Folder 191)
    - Baldwin, Maud, Miss (1878-1926), 33 photographic prints (Box 224, Folder 192)
      Also known as Maud Evangeline Baldwin, Maud E. Baldwin, or Baldwin Studio
    - Bama, Lynne (born 1943), 1 serial (Box 224, Folder 193)
    - Barat, Margaret, Mrs. (born 1835), 2 photographic prints (Box 224, Folder 194)
      Also known as Mrs. G. Barat
    - Bardsley, J., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 224, Folder 195)
    - Barker, J. K., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 224, Folder 196)
      Also known as Mrs. J. Baker
    - Barmore, Emma C., 1 photographic print (Box 224, Folder 197)
    - Barnard, T. M., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 224, Folder 198)
    - Barnes, Lula May, Mrs. (1906-1991), 12 color photographic prints (Box 224, Folder 199)
    - Barrett, C. E., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 224, Folder 200)
      Also known as Mrs. G. N. Barrett
    - Barron, Susan (born 1947), 1 serial (Box 225, Folder 201)
    - Barrow, Reenie Schmerl, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 225, Folder 202)
    - Barth, Charlotte (born 1862), 2 photographic prints (Box 225, Folder 203)
    - Barth, Inger (1858-1952), 12 photographic prints (Box 225, Folder 204)
    - Bartlett, Mary A. (born 1847), 2 photographic prints (Box 225, Folder 205)
      Also known as N. Gray Bartlett
    - Bartley, Sylvia, 2 color photographic prints (Box 225, Folder 206)
    - Barton, Emma (1872-1938), 1 serial (Box 225, Folder 207)
      Also known as Mrs. G. A. (George Albert) Barton
    - Bates, Hatta M., Miss, 4 photographic prints (Box 225, Folder 208)
      Also known as Misses Parsons & Bates
    - Bauder, Maria F., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 225, Folder 209)
      Also known as Mrs. George W. Bauder
    - Bauer, Patricia, 1 color photographic print (Box 225, Folder 210)
      Also known as Pat Bauer
    - Baze, Vicky, 1 color photographic print (Box 225, Folder 211)
      Also known as Vicky Aragon
    - Beauchamp, Jean (1917-2002), 1 color photographic print (Box 225, Folder 212)
    - Bebe, Shahla, 1 color photographic print and 3 color 35mm slides (Box 225, Folder 213)
    - Beck, T., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 225, Folder 214)
    - Beebe, Caroline S., 1 color photographic print (Box 225, Folder 215)
      Also known as Caroline Photography
    - Belcher, Alyson, 5 photographic prints and 20 color 35mm slides (Box 225, Folder 216)
    - Belknap, Hazel, 1 film negatives (Box 225, Folder 217)
    - Belle-Oudry, Gertrude, Mrs. (1881-1953), 3 photographic prints (Box 225, Folder 218)
    - Bemiss, Faith, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 225, Folder 219)
    - Bengtsson, Anna, 1 photographic print (Box 225, Folder 220)
    - Bennett, A. E., Mrs., 4 photographic prints (Box 225, Folder 221)
    - Bennett, Betty Nettis (1927-1996), 235 photographic prints (Box 226-227, Folder 222-234)
    - Bennett, O., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 225, Folder 235)
    - Bennett, Sharon Lynne (born 1950), 7 photographic prints (Box 225, Folder 236)
      Also known as Lynne Bennett
    - Bentzen, Hulda, 2 photographic prints (Box 228, Folder 237)
    - Ben-Yusuf, Zaida, 1 photographic print and 1 color photographic print (Box 228, Folder 238)
      Also known as Zaida Ben Yusuf
    - Berg, Märta, 4 photographic prints (Box 228, Folder 239)
    - Bergdahl, Hanna, 8 photographic prints (Box 228, Folder 240)
    - Berger, J., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 228, Folder 241)
    - Berggrav, Kari, 4 photographic prints (Box 228, Folder 242)
    - Bergh, Lotten, 1 photographic print (Box 228, Folder 243)
      Also known as Lotten Bergh & Co.
    - Berglof, H. M., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 228, Folder 244)
    - Berglund, Anna, 1 photographic print (Box 228, Folder 245)
    - Berglund, Ida, 1 photographic print (Box 228, Folder 246)
      Also known as Ida Berglund-Nyblin
    - Bergström, Emilie, 2 photographic prints (Box 228, Folder 247)
    - Bernhard, Ruth (born 1905), 1 photographic print (Box 228, Folder 248)
    - Berry, Alexia, 2 color 35mm slides (Box 228, Folder 249)
    - Bertha's Studio, 1 photographic print (Box 228, Folder 250)
    - Berthildsson, Bertha, 1 photographic print (Box 228, Folder 251)
    - Bieber, Emilie, Madame (1810-1884), 3 photographic prints (Box 228, Folder 252)
      Also known as E. Bieber
    - Biggerstaff, Candace, 10 color 35mm slides (Box 228, Folder 253)
    - Billström, Mathilda, 1 photographic print (Box 228, Folder 254)
    - Birgén, Ester, 2 photographic prints (Box 228, Folder 255)
    - Birkedahl, Johanne, 3 photographic prints (Box 228, Folder 256)
    - Birkholz, Liz (born 1967), 20 color 35mm slides (Box 228, Folder 257)
    - Bisbee, Mary L., Miss (born 1870), 4 photographic prints and 1 color photographic print (Box 229, Folder 258)
      Also known as Miss Bisbee or Bisbee & Haskins
    - Bisilliat, Maureen (born 1931), 1 serial (Box 229, Folder 259)
      Also known as Sheila Maureen Bisilliat
    - Bitterlicha, Karla J., 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 260)
    - Björkgren, Hulda, 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 261)
    - Björklind, Hildur, 2 photographic prints (Box 229, Folder 262)
    - Björklund, Gurli, 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 263)
      Also known as Gurli Bijorklund
    - Björkzell, Jenny, 2 photographic prints (Box 229, Folder 264)
      Also known as Jenny Björksell
    - Black, Anna E., 2 photographic prints (Box 229, Folder 265)
      Also known as Black Sisters
    - Blickle, Alayne Renée (born 1955), 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 266)
    - Blom, Alma, 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 267)
    - Blomberg, Anna, 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 268)
    - Blomquist, Lydia, 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 269)
    - Blondelu, Gustave, Madame, 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 270)
    - Blue, Shauna Angel, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 229, Folder 271)
    - Blume, Nielsine, 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 272)
    - Bock, Orla, 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 273)
    - Böckmann, Marie, 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 274)
    - Boden, L. B., Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 275)
      Also known as New York Photograph Co.
    - Boderberg, M. E., Mrs., 1 serial (Box 229, Folder 276)
    - Boesen, Anna, 2 photographic prints (Box 229, Folder 277)
    - Bogle, Janice T. (born 1950), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 229, Folder 278)
      Also known as Jan Bogle
    - Bökman, Sophie, 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 279)
    - Boldsen, Julie, 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 280)
    - Bollinger, Gertrude (born circa 1871), 1 photographic print (Box 229, Folder 281)
      Also known as Miss Bollinger
    - Bonfils, Lydie (1837-1918), 1 serial (Box 230, Folder 282)
      Also known as Marie Lydie Cabanis Bonfils or Maison Bonfils
    - Bonney, M. Thérèse (Mabel Thérèse) (1897-1978), 3 photographic prints (Box 230, Folder 283)
      Also known as Therese Bonney
    - Bordnick, Barbara (born 1943), 1 serial (Box 230, Folder 284)
    - Borel, M., Miss, 3 photographic prints (Box 230, Folder 285)
    - Borg, Augusta (1826-1914), 1 photographic print (Box 230, Folder 286)
    - Bos, Dianne (born 1956), 2 photographic prints, 1 color photographic print, and 3 catalogs (Box 230, Folder 287)
    - Bosanquet, Madame, 1 photographic print (Box 230, Folder 288)
    - Boston, Sandra, 3 color photographic prints (Box 230, Folder 289)
    - Bosworth, Rosalys Josephine (1885-1971), 2 photographic prints (Box 230, Folder 290)